<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Impact Analysis on Secure The Bag</title>
    <link>https://example.com/analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Impact Analysis on Secure The Bag</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 17:19:35 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BIP Simulation</title>
      <link>https://example.com/analysis/bip_simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 15:48:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/analysis/bip_simulation/</guid>
      <description>The below simulation results show that OP_SECURETHEBAG is an effective too to reduce network strain in Bitcoin. This is based on the same simulation used in the BIP.
The chart shows how the Bitcoin Mempool will respond during two periods of intense transaction demand. During the first period, rates go back to zero. In the second period, rates remain at the max transactions per second threshold.
The last chart shows that the Mempool is much less congested when using OP_SECURETHEBAG than without it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Optech Newsletter #48</title>
      <link>https://example.com/analysis/optech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 17:31:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/analysis/optech/</guid>
      <description>This article was orignally featured in Bitcoin Optech Newsletter #48, and has been excerpted, abbridged, and updated slightly for accuracy with the most recent iteration of the BIP for this page. The original OpTech content may be found here. OpTech&amp;rsquo;s content is offered under the MIT License.
 The proposed opcode OP_SECURETHEBAG allows an address to commit to one or more branches that require the transaction spending them to include a certain set of outputs, a technique that contract protocol researchers call a covenant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kraken</title>
      <link>https://example.com/analysis/kraken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 17:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/analysis/kraken/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>