<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Impact Analysis on utxos.org -- Bitcoin for Everyone</title><link>https://utxos.org/analysis/</link><description>Recent content in Impact Analysis on utxos.org -- Bitcoin for Everyone</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 21:15:52 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://utxos.org/analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Batching Simulation</title><link>https://utxos.org/analysis/batching_sim/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 15:48:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://utxos.org/analysis/batching_sim/</guid><description>Check Template Verify is a new opcode for Bitcoin which allows transaction issuers to split up their transaction into send and receive components. See https://utxos.org for more information. This is potentially a big benefit because end users can realize faster confirmations on pending transactions.
There is a concern that CTV would result in higher overall chain utilization (because of overhead) than existing batching solutions. Ignoring the benefits that CTV can have for earlier confirmations, it would be bad to introduce a change to Bitcoin that causes users to be wasteful of chain space.</description></item><item><title>Tax Considerations</title><link>https://utxos.org/analysis/taxes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 10:41:53 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://utxos.org/analysis/taxes/</guid><description>In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss basic tax law around payments, establish an analogy between OP_CHECKTEMPLATEVERIFY and traditional certified cheques, and then discuss the relevant tax consequences.
In the &amp;ldquo;legacy&amp;rdquo; financial world, a cheque1 is commonly used to move funds from financial institutions in lieu of inconvenient physical cash transfers. To date, Bitcoin has not needed the concept of a cheque because Bitcoin transactions are direct transfers with no intermediary, i.e., as cash is to a cheque.</description></item><item><title>Congestion Simulation</title><link>https://utxos.org/analysis/bip_simulation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 15:48:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://utxos.org/analysis/bip_simulation/</guid><description>An earlier version of this document used the poission distribution of the average block interval rahter than the exponential, which led to innacurate results. A discussion of this error can be found here. The error in the code has been corrected in the following article, but the diagrams still need to be re-generated.
The below simulation results show that OP_CHECKTEMPLATEVERIFY is an effective too to reduce network strain in Bitcoin. This is based on the same simulation used in the BIP.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin Optech Newsletter #48</title><link>https://utxos.org/analysis/optech/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 17:31:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://utxos.org/analysis/optech/</guid><description>This article was orignally featured in Bitcoin Optech Newsletter #48, and has been excerpted, abbridged, and updated slightly for accuracy with the most recent iteration of the BIP for this page. The original OpTech content may be found here. OpTech&amp;rsquo;s content is offered under the MIT License.
The proposed opcode OP_CHECKTEMPLATEVERIFY allows an address to commit to one or more branches that require the transaction spending them to include a certain set of outputs, a technique that contract protocol researchers call a covenant.</description></item></channel></rss>